Louis Fabian Bachrach Papers
Louis Fabian Bachrach Papers
- Photographs
  - Photographs of famous people
    - John A. Volpe, Sec. Transportation (FB), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Gen. Jonathan Wainwright, U.S. Army (FB), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Henry A. Wallace, vice-pres. U.S. (B) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Earl Warren, Chief Justice U.S. Supreme Court (FB), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Dr. Paul Dudley White (FB), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Wendell L. Willkie (FB), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - George H. Wilkins, Arctic Explorer (FB), 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Roger Wilkins, President, Traveler's Indemnity Corp. (FB), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Roy Wilkins (FB), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Woodrow Wilson, 28th President (B) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Wilson ladies: Mrs. Woodrow, Jessie, Maragaret, Eleanor (LFB), 1920 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ziegfeld, Mrs., See Billie Burke.
    - Efrem Zimbalist, violinist & composer (FB), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Old Defender - Fort McHenry 1814 photographs (DB), 1870 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Gettysburg Battlefield (DB) half stereo photo (DB), 1863 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 2 signed photographs (David Bachrach) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 3 small pictures (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - unidentified (LFB) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - unidentified (R. Frost?) (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Louis Fabian Bachrach, Sr., Material added to collection April 27, 1966
  - Subject file
    - Cartoon
  - Published material
    - Newspaper clippings
      - About Bachrach and Photography
      - By Bachrach about Photography
      - About Others